[
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¯ğŸ‡´", "answer": "Ø§Ù„Ø£Ø±Ø¯Ù†"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡¦", "answer": "Ø§Ù„Ø³Ø¹ÙˆØ¯ÙŠØ©"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¸", "answer": "ÙÙ„Ø³Ø·ÙŠÙ†"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¬", "answer": "Ù…ØµØ±"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¶", "answer": "Ø§Ù„Ø¹Ø±Ø§Ù‚"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡·", "answer": "ØªØ±ÙƒÙŠØ§"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡°ğŸ‡¼", "answer": "Ø§Ù„ÙƒÙˆÙŠØª"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡­", "answer": "Ø§Ù„Ø¨Ø­Ø±ÙŠÙ†"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¶ğŸ‡¦", "answer": "Ù‚Ø·Ø±"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡ª", "answer": "Ø§Ù„Ø¥Ù…Ø§Ø±Ø§Øª"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡´ğŸ‡²", "answer": "Ø¹Ù…Ø§Ù†"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¾ğŸ‡ª", "answer": "Ø§Ù„ÙŠÙ…Ù†"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡±ğŸ‡§", "answer": "Ù„Ø¨Ù†Ø§Ù†"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡¾", "answer": "Ø³ÙˆØ±ÙŠØ§"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡²ğŸ‡¦", "answer": "Ø§Ù„Ù…ØºØ±Ø¨"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¹ğŸ‡³", "answer": "ØªÙˆÙ†Ø³"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡©ğŸ‡¿", "answer": "Ø§Ù„Ø¬Ø²Ø§Ø¦Ø±"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡±ğŸ‡¾", "answer": "Ù„ÙŠØ¨ÙŠØ§"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡¸ğŸ‡©", "answer": "Ø§Ù„Ø³ÙˆØ¯Ø§Ù†"},
  {"question": "ğŸ‡²ğŸ‡º", "answer": "Ù…ÙˆØ±ÙŠØªØ§Ù†ÙŠØ§"}
]
